医生花了大量的时间
doctors spend a lot of time
来思考未来
Focused on the future...
计划未来
Planning it...
并为之奋斗
Working toward it.
但是在某些时刻  你必须意识到
But at some point, you start to realize,
人要活在当下
Your life is happening now...
昨晚有什么事吗
Any changes overnight?
没有
No.
不用等到医学院毕业或是实习期结束
Not after med school, not after residency,
就是现在
Right now.
眼下这一秒
This is it. It's here.
转瞬即逝
Blink and you'll miss it.
是主任叫我  你们最好弄点咖啡
Oh, it's the chief. Somebody better make a coffee run.
一个个看起来都萎靡不振
You all look like hell.
10分钟后我有个外科手术
I gotta be in surgery in ten minutes.
小梅  告诉我这里的情况
Um, mer, will you let me know?
好的
Yeah.
我们也应该去  这里可能还得一会儿
We should go, too. It's probably gonna be a while.
谢博德说她早上就会醒来
Shepherd said she'd wake up in the morning.
他都告诉你什么了  都是废话吗
What did he tell you? Was that all crap?
他到底说什么了
What did he say?
他说可能会需要一点时间
He said it may be a while.
她会醒过来的
She's gonna wake up.
斯蒂文斯还没有醒过来
Stevens still isn't awake.
除了这件事我今天还有好些别的事要忙
And I'm having something of a day even aside from that.
所以  别指望我今天能有什么好脸
So... don't take my face personally.
-今天就这张臭脸了  -你告诉她了吗
- It's just my face today.  - Did you tell her?
还是你来告诉她吧
Uh, you should tell her,
还有  别指望她给你好脸色
And don't take her face personally.
我代表儿童外科部
On behalf of the department of pediatric surgery,
欢迎您加入研究基金计划
I'd like to welcome you to the fellowship program.
你入围了 我们将会为你准备好启动仪式
You're in! We're gonna get you a pair of wheelie sneaks.
祝贺你
Congratulations.
行了
All right.
我知道这过程中我没有很支持你
I know I didn't support you during this process.
不管怎样  现在我力挺你
In any event, I am behind you now.
我努力想在这里做个大人物
I'm trying to be a big person here.
咱们路上再谈行不
How about you meet me halfway?
醒来
Wake up. Wake up.
快醒来
醒醒吧
Wake up. Wake up.
我头好痛
I have a headache.
你醒了
You're up?
你醒了  你对我说话了
You're up and you're talking.
你刚刚说话了是不是
You talked, right?
说话啊
Talk!
我说我头疼   别喊了
Ow. I said I have a headache. Stop yelling.
叫谢博德
Page Shepherd!
抱歉
Ow. I'm sorry.
为什么和欧麦利拥抱啊
Hey, what's with hugging O'malley?
我睡着了  克里斯蒂娜
I slept, Cristina.
昨晚  我第一次睡着了
Last night, I slept for the first time in...
我睡着了
I slept.
这个  我不知道
And, uh, I don't know,
你因为睡着了所以和欧麦利拥抱
Hugging O'malley because you slept?
不是  是因为他收到了好消息
No, I hugged O'malley 'cause he's got great news,
我让他也告诉你  不过我猜
Which I'll let him tell you, but, yeah, I... I guess,
或许我真是因为睡着了所以才和他拥抱
Yeah, maybe I hugged him because I slept.
这都是因为你
And that's because of you,
因为你和我一起去见了我母亲
Because you came with me to see my mom,
然后我睡了个好觉  没有噩梦的一觉
And then I slept, and I slept without nightmares.
这不是个小事情  克里斯蒂娜
That's not a small thing, Cristina.
这  这意味着一切
That... that is everything.
我可以更好的生活了
I can be a better man.
我可以为你做一个更好的男人
I can be a better man for you, and if...
你知道  我希望  如果你愿意的话
I hope, you know, if you'll let me,
我会在你身边  做个更好的男人
I can be a better man with you.
不  什么也别说
No, don't say anything.
考虑一下  好吗
Just... just think about it, okay? Okay?
贝利医生  我想和你说点事
Dr. Bailey, I need to tell you something.
现在不行  欧麦利
Oh, not now, O'malley.
我知道  很快就好
I know. It'll be quick 'cause I gotta
因为我待会儿还要去磨主任
Get to the o.R. To scrub in with the chief.
我想还是先来惹你比较好
Now I think you're gonna be mad at first,
但是我真的想做些有意义的事
But I'm about to do something important,
而且我也很坚持这个决定
And I'm very sure about this decision,
我相信最终你会为我感到骄傲的
And I-I think eventually, you're gonna be proud.
但是在那之前
But, you know, before that,
你可能会说像是
You're probably gonna be like...
"你都干了些什么"
"what did you do?!"
我不是有意模仿你哈
I'm... I don't mean to imitate you...
你这还叫"快"
you call that quick?
我申请了参军做外伤军医
I joined the army to be a trauma surgeon.
明天就去报道
I report for duty tomorrow.
你做了什么
You did what?!
我就知道我们得从这句开始
Yeah, that's where I thought we'd start.
你觉得吗  乔治好像发生了什么事
You know, something's going on with George.
什么
What?
欧文拥抱了他  他们看起来很开心
Owen hugged him. They were happy.
我们开心的时候可不拥抱
Well, we don't hug when we're happy.
你好点了吗
Are you better?
什么
What?
就是你的那个治疗什么的
You know, with your therapy. Uh, whatever.
你说你已经康复了  那你现在还好吗
You said you got well. Well, are you... better?
还是你只是假装没事
Or are you just, you know, fake better?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我是觉得当人们  你知道
I'm asking you if people, you know...
我是说  难道你这么与众不同吗
I mean, are you actually different?
你没觉得什么不一样吗
I mean, do you feel different?
我今天结婚  在市政厅
I'm getting married today. Mm-hmm. City hall.
没有混乱尖叫什么的  一切简洁明了
No muss, no fuss. Just quick and dirty.
你希望我去吗
Well, uh... do you want me to come?
不  不用  只是让你知道一下
No, no. Just letting you know.
不行  你等等
Oh, no, wait. Uh, uh...
这是我的便利贴
Okay, this is my grocery list.
这张是旧的  这张新的
It's old. Uh, this...this is new.
这是我最喜欢的一支笔  所以得还啊  借你的
Um, this is my favorite pen, so I want it back. Borrowed.
这些都是蓝色的  这下你都有了
And all of it's blue, so you're covered.
看吧  如果我们是乔治和欧文
Now see, if we were George and owen,
我们现在就该拥抱
We would hug right now.
天啊
Dude.
未查明身份男性  被巴士拖伤
Unidentified male, dragged by a bus.
他被固定住了  所以我们无法插入喉管
He's clamped down, so we couldn't intubate.
撞了以后他们停下来了吗
Didn't they stop when they hit him?
公车司机不知道他在那
Bus driver didn't know he was there
直到他途中掉在了街上
Until he got halfway down the block.
他会没事吗
Oh, is he gonna be okay?
好了  马上进行心肺复苏
Okay, I'll take over C.P.R.
注射20毫升的依托咪酯和100毫升的SUX
Push 20 etomidate and 100 of sux.
他救了我的命
He saved my life.
公车快撞到我的时候  他把我推了出去
The bus was gonna hit me. He threw me out of the way.
格雷  把她带出去
Grey, get her out of here.
本来该是我被卷在车下的
It was supposed to be me under the bus.
他总是一个人
He's all alone.
他们甚至不知道他是谁  拜托了
They don't even know who he is. Please.
站在这里  不要乱走动
All right, stand over there and just don't move.
恢复了  现在进行外伤手术
He's back. Okay, let's get a trauma series,
准备外伤手术用具和O型血
Trauma labs and o-neg blood in here.
左前臂严重撕裂伤
Severe avulsion injury to the left forearm.
天啊  他的头骨撞裂
Whoa. Okay, his skull is bashed in.
呼叫谢博德和斯隆
Page Shepherd. And Sloan.
注射抗生素  清理伤口
Start antibiotics and start cleaning out those wounds.
现在你能让她出去了么
Now can you get her out of here?
你取出全部了么
Did you get the whole thing?
你把全部的肿瘤都取出了么
Did you get the whole tumor out?
至少让我完成我的检查
Just let me finish my exam.
可以告诉我你的姓名吗
Can you tell me your name?
我叫伊泽贝尔·斯蒂文斯  现在是2009年
My name is isobel Stevens. It's 2009.
这是西雅图圣恩医院精神科重症加护病房
And I'm in the... neuro I.C.U. At Seattle Grace hospital.
你把那鬼东西取出来了吗
Did you get the damn thing out?
全部取出来了
Got the whole damn thing.
你成功了
You got it? Yeah.
上帝啊  你取出了全部的
Oh, god. You got the whole thing.
而且我还能说话  也知道自己的名字
And I can talk and I know my name
-而且我没变棵大头菜  -你不是
- And I'm not a turnip.  - Nope.
没有恶意
No offense. Oh, no.
你是个很棒的外科医生  但是我真的以为
You are a great surgeon, but I really thought
我会变成一棵大头菜、
I was gonna be a turnip.
这真是太棒了
This is so unbelievably great.
你的肾脏还未完全恢复
Your kidneys are a little sluggish,
所以我们得再观察电解质几个小时
So we're just gonna keep an eye on your electrolytes for a few hours.
-术后反应良好  -很好  很好
- Your post-op crit was... was fine. - Okay, good. Good.
手术怎么样
How did the surgery go?
拿掉肿瘤了吗  取出来了吗
Did you get the brain tumor? Did you get it out?
伊兹  你刚刚问过了
Iz, you just asked him that.
我们跟你说过了
We just talked about it.
没事的  这种迟缓症状会持续一会儿
No, no, it's okay. She's gonna be foggy for a while.
肿瘤切掉了
The tumor's out.
当时有一点出血
There was a little bleeding during the post...
-你切掉肿瘤了吗  -没错
- You got it? - Yeah.
全部切掉了吗
All of it?
太棒了
That's amazing.
德里克·谢博德  你是一个英雄
Derek Shepherd, you are a hero.
我还记得他是德里克·谢博德
And I know that that's Derek Shepherd.
你是阿历克斯  你应该吻我
And you're Alex. And you should kiss me.
阿历克斯
Alex...
我没有脑瘤了
I don't have a brain tumor.
我什么肿瘤都没有了
I'm tumor-free.
是的  没有肿瘤了
Yes, you are.
怎么了  你怎么表情这么怪
What's wrong? Why do you look weird?
没有啊  没什么
No, nothing. Nothing.
你的肾脏恢复还有点迟缓
Uh, your kidneys are a little slow.
我们得再观察一阵
We're just gonna watch them.
好的  你一小时候后要复查电解质是吧
Okay. So you'll just recheck my electrolytes in an hour?
好的
Okay.
手术怎么样
How did the surgery go?
拿掉肿瘤了吗
Did you get the tumor?
拿掉了
We did.
肿瘤切掉了
The tumor's gone.
当时有一点出血
There was a little bit of bleeding,
我们也处理好了
And we took care of that.
你切掉肿瘤了
You got it?
天哪
Oh, my god.
我可以说话了  我没死
And I can talk, and you didn't kill me.
你们都怎么了  我们应该庆祝才对
What's wrong with you people? We should be celebrating.
她跟那个不记得老公已过世的女人一样
She's like the woman who couldn't remember her husband was dead.
每隔五分钟我们就得再告诉她一次
We had to keep telling her every five minutes.
可能是正常的术后反应迟钝
Could be a perfectly normal post-operative haze.
或者是手术中的出血损害了短期记忆
Or the bleeding during the procedure blitzed her short-term retention.
-你是不是伤到她脑子哪里了  -克莱夫
- Did you screw up her brain? - Karev...
我一会儿回来  冷静点
I'll be back. Try and stay calm.
吓着她起不了任何作用
Freaking her out is not gonna help.
快醒来
Wake up.
-人车对撞  -车赢了
- Man versus bus. - The bus won.
检查他的左臂
Check out the left arm.
他又不行了
He's crashing again!
-什么情况  -车祸
- What do we got? - We got roadkill.
让一下  他冲到一辆行驶的公车前面
You mind? He stepped out in front of a moving bus
去救路中间的一个女的  他可是个英雄
So he could pull a woman out of the way. He's a hero.
-你能治好手臂吗  -手指已经有血色了
- Can you fix the arm? - Fingers are already blue.
如果能  也要几个小时以后了
If it's gonna happen, it's gotta be in the next few hours.
瞳孔放大  停止心脏复苏术
Pupil's blown. Stop C.P.R.
把颅骨钻递给我
Okay, give me a cranial drill, please.
格蕾  想实践一下吗
Grey, want to practice your burr holes?
护士  请稳住他的颈部
Stabilize his neck, please, nurse.
好  把钻子给她
Okay, hand her the drill.
慢慢钻进去  感觉卡住时  停下来
Okay, go in slowly. When you feel it grab, stop,
否则会伤到大脑的
'Cause otherwise you're gonna be hitting the brain.
好了  开始  要快
Okay, let's go. Quickly.
就那里了
Right there!
拉出来  拉出来  停下
Pull back, pull back! That's it.
干得不错  格雷医生
Nice work, Dr. Grey.
我去拿点杆菌肽来处理他的脸
I'm gonna go get some bacitracin for that face.
好了  把他的头转过来  慢点
All right. Let's get his head rotated. Easy.
你醒来了  先生
Welcome back, sir.
我们可担心了好一会儿
You had us worried there for a minute.
你觉得他能撑过来吗
You think he's gonna make it?
希望如此
I hope so.
他真的得撑过来
He really has to make it.
斯隆医生
Dr. Sloan.
你这样缝会很紧
There's gonna be too much tension.
重新做一个分层缝合吧
Start over and do a layered closure.
我能具体问下吗
Can I ask a question about that?
好吧  你提出要搬到一起住
Okay. You brought up moving in together
还有结婚  我含糊其词
And marriage, and I put it off.
所以你觉得尴尬了
And now you're embarrassed
你不愿看我的眼睛
And you won't make eye contact with me because
因为你觉得我占了强势
You feel that I have all the power in the relationship,
但我并不想做恋爱关系里强势的那一方
But I don't want all the power in the relationship.
我很乐意你来做这个  我们能不说这个了吗
I...I'm happy to share it. Can we just skip this part?
去拿点4-0缝线来重新缝合
Get some 4-0 vicryl so you can redo your patient's sutures.
我会装着什么都没听见的
I'll totally pretend I didn't hear any of that.
一向是女人对我那样做的
Women do this to me.
我从来不说  我们搬到一起住吧
I don't do this. "Let's get a house together."
当女孩子这方不好受吧
Sucks being the girl, huh?
我才不是女的
I'm not the girl.
女孩子会怎么做
What do girls do?
我们先是让对方吃闭门羹
Well, we start with the cold shoulder,
所以你做得刚刚好
So you're right on track.
然后我们跟闺蜜去抱怨
And we go to our girlfriends and we bitch,
闺蜜就会说  你想拥有未来
And our girlfriends say, "you want to build a future,
就自己去努力
"build it yourself.
你不需要一个男的来给你这一切
"you don't need a man to give you that.
你想买房子
"so you want to buy a house?
那就买去
Just buy a house."
你很擅长这个呀
You're good at this.
我该去当爱情顾问
I ought to help someone get a love life.
我自己的可不怎么样
I suck at my own.
他冲到车前面  就为了救我
He jumped in front of a bus... for me.
-你对欧麦利做了什么  -什么
- What did you do to O'malley? - Excuse me?
这里还有其他人可能会劝别人
Uh, somebody else around here likely to convince someone
参军去伊拉克当战地医生的吗
To join the army and be a trauma surgeon in Iraq?
什么  参军
What?! The army?!
什么
What?
心室纤维颤动  充电360伏
V-fib. Charge the paddles to 360.
找下关系  把这事撤了
Just call who you have to call and undo this.
贝利医生  这里正忙着呢
Dr. Bailey, little busy here.
-让开  -乔治  乔治·欧麦利
- Clear. - George? George O'malley?
-这不是我的主意  -没有反应
- It wasn't my idea. - No change.
-再来一次  -让开
- Charge again. - Clear.
我尽我所能教他干好外伤科
I did what I could to give him a decent education in trauma.
我并不知道他会去参军
I didn't know he was gonna go and enlist.
-他快不行了  -找到原因了
- He keeps coding. - Here's why...
开书型骨盆骨折
open-book pelvic fracture.
出血太多
There's too much bleeding.
现在送他去手术室他也会死在手术台上
We take him to an O.R. Now, he'll die on the table.
他得做血管造影术来抑制
He needs to go to angio if we're gonna stop
-骨盆动脉出血  -窦性心搏  有波动了
- The pelvic arterial bleeding. - Sinus tach. We have a rhythm.
-跳动很小  但有跳动  -稳住骨盆
- It's barely there, but it's there. - Let's stabilize the pelvis.
我知道医院里发生的事
I know what goes on in this hospital.
我知道战争让你变得一团糟
I know you're messed up from that war,
还不仅仅是些小事  别把他也搅进来
And not in a small way. Get him out of it.
需要我就呼我  我还有其他病人
Page me if you need me. I've got other patients.
你怎么把所有女的都惹了
How'd you piss off all the women?
带他去做血管造影术吧
Um, let's get our guy to angio.
血管造影术吗  他脉搏都没有
Angio? He's barely got a pulse.
现在不做就保不住他的命了
It's now or never if we want him to live.
走吧
Let's move.
先生  我知道不容易
Sir, I know it's tough,
但如果接下来几分钟你努力熬过去
But I'd personally be very grateful
我感激不尽
If you'd try and stay alive for the next few minutes.
也许儿科比普外科要生气勃勃些
Maybe we're bouncier in peds than in general surgery,
但我原以为你会大叫
But I thought that there would be a "yay"
或者跳起来呢
Or some jumping around.
因为作为一个获得顶级奖学金的人
'cause you look pretty dour for someone
你真是有点沉默了
Who's about to start a highly prized fellowship.
你是获得顶级奖学金了  是吧
You are about to start a highly prized fellowship, right?
我想到法子阻止乔治了  你一起干吗
Hey, I've got a plan to stop George. Are you in?
阻止乔治什么
Stop George from what?
他参军了  好  一起干
He joined the army. Yes, I'm in.
贝利  我跟你说话呢
Bailey, I'm talking to you.
你为什么要阻止他
Why are you trying to stop him?
-因为他参军了  -还有呢
- Because he joined the army. - And?
还有他是我的前夫
And because he's my ex-husband,
我还认识他的母亲  还很喜欢她
And I know his mom and I love his mom,
还有通常情况下伊兹会劝他的
And normally Izzie would talk sense into him,
但她现在得了癌症  脑部损伤还挺严重
But she's got cancer and kind of a bad mental deficit,
所以阻止他是我的责任了
So it's on me to stop him.
但你为什么想要阻止他
But why would you want to stop him?
因为他参军了
Because he joined the army.
你不觉得这是个问题吗
Don't you think that's a problem?
我觉得这样做很了不起
I think that's awesome.
了不起
Awesome?
你不嚼一下吗
You gonna chew?
我那被车压的病人在做血管造影术
My dragged-under-a-bus guy's in angio,
他们随时都可能呼我
And they're gonna page me any minute.
伊兹怎么样了  还有重复说话吗
How's Izzie? Is she reiterating anything?
没有了
No.
下午6点  你们的白痴同事
OK. At 6:00 P.M. your idiotic collegue
乔治·欧麦利会做完跟主任一起的手术
George O'malley would finish his surgery with the chief.
下午6点  你们会聚集到手术室外走廊
And at 6 P.M. you will be standing beside this in the O.R. hallway
投入到一场干涉活动里
Prepared to join an intervention.
什么  友好的人可能会把这称为干涉
What? Polite company might call it intervention
但我可不确定干涉也包括
Though I'm not sure interventions
在背后拿着鞭子吆喝人
Involve whooping people on the behind with a belt.
-怎么了  他现在酗酒了吗  -他参军了
- What, he's got a drinking problem now? - He joined the army.
什么  007吗  他怎么可能参军
What?! 007? He can't go to army.
他会被打死的
He's the guy that gets killed.
还是自己擦枪走火而死的
He's that guy who gets killed cleaning his own gun.
格蕾去动之以情
Grey is going to coax him back as a loving friend.
你们去晓之以理
You are going to use logic and reason
指出他这种做法有多蠢
To point out the idiocy of his ways.
斯蒂文斯会用癌症之人的眼睛眼巴巴看着他
Stevens will make sad cancer eyes.
如果这么做还行不通  克莱夫
And if all of that doesn't work, Karev, you're gonna pull out
你就出你那张我是在垃圾箱边长大的悲情牌
Your "I was raised out back with the trash cans" roots
-狠狠打击他  -6点是吧
- And just beat the crap out of him. - 6:00.
6点
6:00.
嗨
Hey there.
我知道这有点吓人  如果能让你觉得好受
I know this must be scary, but if it's any consolation,
你真是个孤胆英雄
You're a hard-core hero.
你救了那个女人
You saved that woman's life.
他是不是想写些什么
I-is he trying to write something?
你握得住吗
Can you hold this?
好吧
Oh, okay.
你明天就有力气了
You'll be stronger tomorrow.
通知一号手术室  让他们准备好
Call O.R. One. Tell 'em to get ready for him.
阿曼达  你不能来这里
Amanda, you can't be out here.
换做是你  这个时候你想一个人待着吗
Would you want to be all alone at a time like this?
在他救我前
We had 30 seconds of interaction
我们有30秒的接触
Before he saved my life,
我还很不友好
And... and I wasn't even nice.
我当时站在一个角落
I was standing on a corner when this...
这个相貌平平的男人就站在我旁边对我笑
Ordinary-looking guy stands next to me and smiles,
而我却忙着
And... and I'm so busy
跟帅哥搭讪
Scoping for someone hotter that...
我正眼都没瞧他
I don't even give him a second look.
接着我就只知道  他把我从
And next thing I know, he throws me
车前推开了 本来我是在前面的
Out of the way of a bus I'm about to walk in front of
现在他自己却差点儿丧命
And almost gets himself killed.
我真的情何以堪
He literally... he swept me off my feet.
床上躺的是我的王子啊
That is my prince in that bed.
好吧  你可以待到他们把他带去手术室前
Okay, you can stay until they take him to surgery.
-别不识相  -要是你再离开我
Uh, not a good time. You know what? You walk away from me again,
我保证我一定会扯住你的头发  然后用力拉
I swear I will grab you by the hair and pull hard.
我可是爱丽桑那
I grew up with the name Arizona.
我在游乐场上学会了怎么玩阴的
I learned how to play dirty on the playground.
我情愿冒风险  你是我的选择
I stuck my neck out for you. You were my pick.
我很感谢这一切  但这是个重要的决定
And I appreciate that, but it's a big decision.
坦白说来  这是个很好的机会
It's not, frankly. It's the brass ring.
代价昂贵的  很有竞争力的机会
It's the most exclusive, it's the most competitive,
而且我们也完全够格
And we're as good as it gets.
没有人挡路没有人不赞成
Nobody lands this thing and says no.
我丈夫昨天跟我说
My husband informed me yesterday
如果我接受了儿科奖学金
That if I accept the peds fellowship,
如果我签了训练两年的合同
If I sign on for another two years of training
伴随着无止尽的工作时间和超强负荷
And the hours and the workload that come with it
当我成为主治外科医生
When I could be a general surgery attending
然后才回家准备晚餐时
And make it home for dinner,
他会向我提出离婚
He will divorce me.
这是个重要的决定
It's a big decision.
拯救那只手臂会是件不太容易的事
You're gonna have a hard time saving that arm.
如果我能及时到那一步的话
I can get him back to full function
我可以让它完全恢复
If I can get there in time.
-我在考虑买个房子  -非常好啊
- I'm thinking about buying a house.  - Good for you.
我和梅瑞狄斯下午要去市政厅
Meredith and I are gonna go to city hall this afternoon.
-我们要结婚了  -真的吗
- We're getting married.  - Really?
是的
Mm-hmm.
-好消息  -我知道
- That's great news.  - I know.
如果我能救斯蒂文斯
If I could just save Stevens...-
你有权利获得幸福  你有权利步入婚姻殿堂
You're allowed to be happy. You're allowed to get married.
你有这权利
You've earned that right.
恭喜  你这幸运的家伙
Congratulations, you lucky bastard.
来  给个拥抱
Come here. Give me a hug.
为什么今天大家都在拥抱
Why is everyone hugging today?
哇  娇羞新娘哎
Oh, the blushing bride.
好了  说下那位无名氏的方案
All right, here is the plan for our john doe.
谢博特  你负责抽空膜上出血
Shepherd, you'll evacuate the epidural.
我和格蕾负责内伤
Grey and I will correct the internal injuries.
这样就给出空来让托瑞斯安置内部固定器
That'll make room for Torres to place the internal fixator.
斯隆  你还应该会有些时间来处理那手臂
Sloan, you should still have time to work on the arm
如果病人没有出现酸中毒或体温过低
If the patient doesn't get too acidotic or hypothermic.
你认为他能活下来吗
Do you think he has a shot?
我见过更糟糕的也挺了过来
I've seen people come back from worse.
我以为你在外科
Hey, I thought you were in surgery.
- 我马上去  -你有跟贝利医生提
- I'm on my way. Have you talked to Bailey
基金和塔克吗
About this peds and Tucker thing?
没有  我和贝利只谈了乔治参军的事
No, I talked to Bailey about the army thing and George.
你是在和我闹别扭吗
Are you upset with me?
不  我很好
No, I'm awesome.
-卡利奥普  -别 别这么叫我
你说的那很好
You said it was awesome.
乔治  可爱的友好的乔治  他连苍蝇都不杀的
George...sweet, kind George who can't even kill a fly...
却要参军去伊拉克了
Is joining the army to go to Iraq
卷入战争中  而你却说这很赞
In the middle of a war, and you said "awesome."
这的确很赞啊
It is awesome.
不  这不好  天啊  你怎么会这样
No, it is not awesome. God! Who are you?
-手臂怎么样  -神经依旧完整
- How's the arm?  - The nerves are still intact.
-只需要重建下血管  -我能开始了吗
- Just have to reattach the vessels.  - You ready for me?
我已经搞定大部分内压伤
I'm almost done with the major internal crush injuries.
骨盆马上就归你管了
Pelvis will be all yours in a minute.
再给我些纱布
Give me some more laps, please.
你搞的定吗
You think you could do it?
阻止别人的计划
Step in front of a bus for a perfect stranger?
希望可以吧
We'd all like to think we would, but...
不管怎样将军亨特已经在努力了
that's more or less major hunt's been doing
-每天像是最后一天  -不对  男人都这样
Every day for the last couple of years. Oh, no, the guys did.
我只是在背后默默支持
I just came in behind 'em
带着扫帚簸箕狂干
With a dustpan and a broom and swept up.
你在战火中缝合士兵的伤口
You sewed up soldiers under fire.
你不是清洁工
You didn't sweep up.
你觉得欧麦利在那里会怎么样
How do you think O'malley is gonna do over there?
-你觉得他能行么  -我不觉得
- You think...you think he can handle it?  - No, I don't.
我倒觉得他会让我们大吃一惊的
I think he's gonna surprise us all.
我觉得他会被装在收尸袋里运回来
I think he's coming back in a body bag.
我觉得你们就都该闭嘴
I think you all should just shut up.
闭上你们的嘴
Just shut the hell up.
拜托了  别再说了
Please. Shut up.
"谢博德切除了你的所有肿瘤"
"Shepherd got your whole tumor out."
天啊
Oh, my god.
阿历克斯  你为什么不告诉我  天啊
Alex, why didn't you tell me? Oh, my god.
但是我们在继续努力
But we're working on it.
你记得今天早上你什么时候醒的吗
You remember what time you woke up this morning?
不记得
Um, not exactly.
7:45
7:45.
7:45 "欧麦利参军了"吗
7:45. "O'malley joined the army"?
-什么  -是的  他要去伊拉克当个外科医生
- What?  - Yeah, he's gonna be a trauma surgeon in iraq.
你什么时候醒的
When'd you wake up?
-7：45  他会死的  -恩 我们在解决这事
-7:45. He's gonna get killed. - Yeah, we're dealing with it.
你知道乔治那事吗
Did you know about this George thing?
是的  那个草包
Yep. Canon fodder.
我来取些血
I'm just gonna take some more blood.
上次检查  你的血钾浓度是6.3
Last time we checked, your potassium was 6.3.
-你什么时候醒的  -早些时候  我记不清
- When'd you wake up? - Um, early. I can't quite remember. I...
7:45.6.3.7:45
7:45. 6.3. 7:45.
"欧麦利要参军"  乔治吗
"O'malley joined the army"? George?
我们在解决这事
We're dealing with it.
你的血钾浓度是多少
What's your potassium?
额  我
Uh, I...
-伊兹  你的血钾是多少  -你知道么
- Iz, what's your potassium? - You know what?
就给那病理表读读
Why don't we just give her the chart to read
让她试着记忆  好吗
And try and memorize, okay?
然后我可以和你谈谈她的高血钾
And I can talk to you about her hyperkalemia.
她刚接受过脑部手术
Look, she just had brain surgery
以及很有杀伤力的白介素2流程
And an incredibly aggressive course of I.L.-2.
她需要休息
She needs rest.
她需要在记忆全消失前
She needs to exercise whatever memory she's got left
锻炼它
Before it all turns to mush.
就算你像个野蛮人那样吼她
Well, she's not gonna heal
她也不会马上好
With you barking orders at her like a caveman.
走开  杨
Butt out, Yang.
不  她是我的病人  我不管你是她的丈夫
No, she's my patient. I don't care if you're her husband.
听着  你知道我可以马上把你的探病时间
Look, she... you want to see how fast I can get your visiting hours
-取消  -她签了不抢救协议  她签了那该死的东西
- Down to zero?  - She signed a d.N.R. She signed a frigging d.N.R.
而且还逼我保证她会过着正常生活
And made me promise she'd come outta this with a life.
不在那病床上没有她的思想
Not in a hospital bed, not with no brain,
我必须得保证她有正常的生活
I had to promise she'd have a life.
你想知道她无法再记忆
You want to know what happens
就会发生什么吗
If she can't make any new memories?
忘记自己是个医生
Forget about being a doctor.
她就需要全面监护
She's gonna need round-the-clock babysitters.
我们一起买了房子  而她却
We get an apartment together, and she can't ever
都不能找到去卫生间的路
Find her way to the damn toilet.
天知道她会不会摔一跤
Tracker on her ankle in case, god forbid,
-或者在门口徘徊  -阿历克斯 你做的到的
- She wanders out the front door! - Alex, you can handle this.
她会好起来的
She will get better.
或许会  或许不会  这要靠我
Maybe. Maybe not. It's on me.
她的未来就靠我了
Her future is on me.
他会好起来吗
Is he gonna be okay?
到早上我们会知道更多情况
We'll know more in the morning.
进去吧
Go ahead.
她怎么样了  好点了没
How's she doing? Any better?
-没有  -该死
-No.  -Damn.
我要去市政厅了
Well, I'm going to city hall
去把事儿办了
To go do the thing.
真的吗  貌似今天不怎么合适吧
Seriously? It doesn't seem like the day for it.
看看阿历克斯
Look at Alex.
他一整天都那么努力
He's in there working so hard all day,
她却完全不知道
And she doesn't know.
如果她一直这样下去
And if she stays like this,
可能她永远都不会知道  他有多么爱她
She may never know how much he loves her.
还有那个叫阿曼达的女孩
And that girl amanda...
在那里爱着那个陌生人
She's in there loving a stranger.
她认为那是她的白马王子
She thinks that's her prince charming. Mm.
我想说  也许他今天会死  有这种可能
I mean, he's probably gonna die today, chances are.
所以  我要去结婚
So yeah, I'm gonna go get married.
因为我觉得应该花点时间
Because I think it's important to take the time
告诉你爱着的人你多爱他们
To tell the people you love how much you love them
在他们能听你说的时候
While they can hear you.
我爱你  克里斯蒂娜·杨
I love you, Cristina Yang.
你变了
You have changed.
可能变了吧
Mm. Maybe I have.
怎么了
What?
给你个拥抱
I'm gonna hug you.
也许我不了解别人
Maybe I don't understand people,
看不透事情
I don't see things.
也许我只是不明白
So maybe I just don't get
你怎么回事  为什么这么生气
What's going on with you or why you're so mad,
我还是认为这很棒
But I do think it's awesome.
-我认为乔治去当兵很棒  -闭嘴
I think that George joining the army is awesome. Um, shut up.
就不  你问我是怎样的人
Um, no. You asked me who I was.
我是这样的人  觉得乔治这么做很危险
I am a person who thinks that what George is doing
也很可怕  同样很勇敢
Is dangerous and terrifying and brave.
他将为国家服务
He's going to serve his country.
为保卫人民而冒生命危险
He's going to risk his life to save the men and women
他是让我们安枕无忧的人
Who make it possible for you and i to sleep safely in our beds.
我认为这是很勇敢的事情
I'm a person who thinks that that is brave.
我曾在飞机上吊架上
And I am a person who stood in an airplane hanger
看着他们把我哥哥的棺材卸下来
And watched them unload my brother's body in a coffin...
我们只得到一面国旗
And all we got was a flag.
我哥哥死在战场上
My brother died over there
凯利  因为那里缺医生
Because there weren't enough doctors, Callie.
所以在我看来  乔治·欧麦利是个爱国者
So for my money, George O'malley is a patriot.
是英雄
He's a hero,
我感谢他的存在
And I am grateful that he exists.
所以没错  我说了"真棒"
So yeah, the word I use is "awesome."
这就是我
That's who I am.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
-抱歉  我不知道  -没事  等一下
-Sorry, I-I didn't realize...  -Oh, no, no, wait.
我  爱  你
I... love...You.
我也爱你
Well, I-I-I love you, too.
不  只是
No, just...
我爱你
I love you.
我说出来了  我说了"我爱你"
I said... I said "i love you."
我说了
Me.
克里斯蒂娜·杨
Cristina Yang.
你伤到我了
You traumatized me.
你知道我不是故意的  对于那件事我很抱歉
And you know that I am s... I am so sorry about...
该死的  我不是在讲你快把我掐死那事
Oh, no, damn it. Not about the choking.
是  你来到这里  去除我内心的冰椎
It's... It's like you come here and then you pull out my icicle
让我爱上了你  但是我不能
And you make me love you, and I can't...
我的意思是  我不想
I mean, I don't want to...
我  我已经不能
I-I can't breathe...
离开你了
Without you.
你可以的  克里斯蒂娜  我们可以的
You can do this. Cristina, we can do this.
你所必须做的事只是离我远点
All you have to do is just meet me halfway.
你所能做的事情就是肯定自己
All you have to do is say yes.
感觉怎么样
What's your crit?
难吃死了
This is disgusting.
真不能想象我们把这给病人吃
I can't believe we serve it to the patients.
你一直嚷嚷着要柠檬果冻
"you keep asking for lime jell-o
我不喜欢吃这东西
And don't like it."
别把它丢给我
So stop giving it to me.
因为你变傻了而我没有
You get mad if I don't.
好了  感觉怎么样
Okay, now what's your crit?
我不知道  我很累了
I don't know. I'm tired.
欧麦利明天打算做什么
What's O'malley doing tomorrow?
参军
Joining the army.
好吧  我要休息了
Yeah. I need a break.
你以为我不想休息吗  你给我忍耐
You don't think I need a break? Suck it up.
什么  天啊
What...god.
够了
Back off.
如果你很难接受的话  我很抱歉
I'm sorry if this is hard for you,
但是你不是那个
But you are not the one
患有短时记忆的病人
With the short-term memory of a carrot.
好啊  继续啊  把不爽都发泄出来啊
Hey. Go ahead. Get it off your chest.
这又不像我只有5分钟的短暂记忆
It's not like I'm gonna remember in five minutes.
够了  我不是那个脑袋有问题的人
Okay, I'm not the one with a carrot for a brain
但我的太太是
but I'm married to
我们走向教堂的原因是
it 'cause of some crock of a wedding We walked into,
唯一原因是我们两个都
and only because The two of us thought
认为你会在一个星期内走完你的人生
you'd be dead within a week.
你让我想你保证不要让你这样活着
You made me promise you that you wouldn't live like this.
该死的  你现在想我怎样做
So now what the hell am I supposed to do,
用枕头把你给闷死吗
Smother you with a pillow,
给你注射过量的吗啡
Shoot you up with a-an overdose of morphine?
想都别想  离开你
Not really psyched about that. Leave you?
更是想都别想
Not really psyched about that either.
所以觉得我有点犯迷糊  对吧
So I guess I'm kinda screwed, right?
我至少不像你这样差劲
I mean, not as bad as you,
但我也不想将来独自一人在公园里散步
But not a frigging walk in the park, either.
对不起  伊玆
I'm sorry, iz.
没关系
No.
我叫你发泄出来的嘛  你发泄了
I told you to get it off your chest. You did.
你忘记了没有
Did you forget yet?
我也希望忘记了  但还没有
Nope. Not yet.
给我一分钟
Give me a minute.
如果我在普外科有什么做的不好的地方
If there's still a spot for me in general surgery,
我希望你能给我指点指点
I'd like to take you up on that.
我花了几个月时间想训练你
I spent months trying to talk you off peds.
我快成功的时候  你改变主意了
I finally get on board, and you change your mind?
塔克给了我最后通牒
Tucker gave me an ultimatum...
选择事业还是婚姻
The fellowship or our marriage.
你选了你的婚姻
You chose your marriage.
不是  我选择离开他
No, I'm leaving him,
因为如果婚姻要依靠最后通牒来维系的话
Because a marriage that resorts to ultimatums,
它已经丧失其本义了
That's not a marriage.
我的意思是  那是什么样的老公才会做的事啊
I mean, what kind of husband does that?
所以说  我快变成单亲妈妈
So... I'm going to be a single mom.
这不是去操作
It's not the time for...
新的专业设备的时候
New specialties.
该死的
Damn.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这是我第一次把事情说出来
It's just the first time I said it out loud,
所以我才会有点失控
So it just kinda took the wind out of me.
玛兰达  你决定了吗
Miranda, are you sure about this?
我的意思是  他也许会回心转意的
I mean, he might come around.
他  他只是害怕了
He... he's just scared.
我们都很害怕
Well, we're all scared.
我的意思是  如果你不害怕的话就不会注意
I mean, if you're not scared, you're not paying attention.
我的一个住院医生要上战场了
O-one of my residents just signed up to go to war.
多可怕啊
That's scary.
另一个则被恶性黑素瘤弄得快死了
Another one just almost lost her life to melanoma.
现在她连今天是什么日子都不知道
Now she doesn't know what day it is.
这多可怕啊
That's scary.
塔克的事情根本就不值得害怕
What Tucker's facing isn't scary.
他只是软弱
He's just weak.
不  你这样的安慰是不能解决问题的  先生
No, a pat on the back isn't gonna help, sir.
好吧  我要离开吗
Okay. Um, should I go? Uh...
好的
Okay.
好吧
我就站在这里陪你
I'll just stand here with you
这样可以了吗
If that's all right.
可以了  先生
Yes, sir.
这样就很好了
That would be fine.
我以为你在给无名氏做手术呢
I thought you were operating on john doe.
做完了  现在我在看房子
I already did. Right now I'm looking at houses.
我喜欢那个有石头壁炉的
One has a stone fireplace, which I like.
这个有向蒙大拿州一样大的后院
This one has a backyard the size of montana.
你要买房子
You're buying a house?
是的
Yeah.
很好
Right. Okay.
我正打算买间房子
I'm buying a house right now.
我打算趁现在这时机买房
It's a buyer's Market, and I'm buying a house.
你买房的唯一动机
The only reason that you're even talking about a house
就是让我感觉很差劲
Is to make me feel bad.
你只是想向我证明你要搬离我了
You're trying to prove that you're moving on without me
然后我就会后悔最后改变主意
So then I'll regret my decision and change my mind.
好吧  这是女人们谈到搬家
Okay, is this what women are doing
这个字的时候的反应吗
When they say they're moving on?
是的
Yeah.
他们通常不会贷款买房的  但是
They don't usually take out a home loan to do it, but...
真可怜  我们说清楚吧  我要搬家
pathetic. Let me be clear. I'm moving on.
我比你更懂女人
I'm a better woman than you.
可以走了吗
Ready to go?
我刚接到通知  我们的无名氏还需要做手术
I just got a page. Our john doe needs to go back into surgery.
是的  他术后的CT表示有出血现象
Yeah. His post-op c.T. Showed a re-bleed.
我叫了尼尔森去做了
I'm gonna have nelson take care of it.
不会吧  真的吗
No, really?
是的  虽然我比较希望自己做
Yeah. Well, I'd prefer to do it myself,
但我得照看伊玆
But I want to check in on Izzie.
或许我们先做完手术再去结婚
Maybe we can go do that first and then go get married after?
不行
No, we can't
因为回来后我们还要跟乔治谈一下参军的问题
Because we have the George intervention after that.
我会叫尼尔森搞定的
I'll have nelson do it.
不如这样  让他们去拦住他
You know what? Tell them to prep him.
我们跑去市政厅  再回来  就这样做吧
We'll run to city hall, we'll come back.And we'll do it then.
梅瑞狄斯
Meredith...
不  你明白吗  我们走吧  我们得去
No, you know, let's go. We gotta go.
我们要跑去市政厅  再回来
We gotta run to city hall, we'll come back,
你可以去查看伊玆的情况  我们可以监看无名氏的情况
You'll check on Izzie, we'll monitor john doe,
我还可以去劝住乔治  让他放弃参军的念头  你看
I'll go talk George out of joining the army... look,
我们可以改天再结婚的
We could do this another day.
没有改天的  每天都是这样的
There is no other day. Every day is like this.
这里每天都是重要时刻  没有时间了
Every day there's a crisis. There's no time.
梅瑞狄斯
Meredith...
我爱你  我真的想今天嫁给你
I love you, and I do want to marry you today,
但是现在没有时间
But there is no time.
你有白纸吗
You have a piece of paper?
干嘛啊
For what?
我想跟你永远在一起
I want to be with you forever,
你想跟我永远在一起吗
And you want to be with me forever.
因此  我们需要订立誓约
And in order to do that, we need to make vows,
承诺书  合约
A commitment, a contract.
给我纸
Give me a piece of paper.
我没有啊
I don't.
我  没  有
I-I-I don't.
我只有便条纸
I-I have post-its.
也行
Okay.
我们需要对方定下什么誓约呢
What do we want to promise each other?
你要永远爱我
That you'll love me...
就算在你讨厌我的时候也要爱我
Even when you hate me.
即使在讨厌对方的时候也要爱护对方
To love each other even when we hate each other.
不能逃离对方  任何时候
No running... ever.
无论什么事情都不能与对方分开
Nobody walks out no matter what happens.
不逃离对方  然后呢
No running. What else?
我们要珍惜爱护对方
That we'll take care of each other
即使我们又老  又臭  又懵
Even when we're old and smelly and senile,
如果我有老年痴呆症  忘记了你呢
And if I get alzheimer's and forget you...
我会每天提醒你我是你的谁
I will remind you who I am every day.
当我们又老  又臭  又懵的时候要照顾对方
To take care when old, senile... and smelly.
这
This...
誓约的效力是  一生一世
Is forever.
签名
Sign.
这就是我们的婚礼  便条纸婚约
This is our wedding, a post-it?
在你确认签名后生效
Mm-hmm. If you sign it.
现在要干什么
Now what?
现在我要亲吻新娘了
Now I kiss the bride.
结婚了
Married.
看见了吗
See that?
时间很充足吧
Plenty of time.
要做E.K.G.了
Gotta do an e.K.G.
怎么了  没有悄悄话要讲吗
What, I don't even get any small talk?
你怎么了
What's your problem?
好吧  我跟你说
Well, I'll tell you.
我知道我该感恩
I know that I'm supposed to be grateful
因为我能  重生
For my "new lease on life,"
但阿历克斯在这告诉我
But Alex marched in here and basically told me
他说和我结婚
That being married to me
是他做过最糟糕的决定
Was the worst thing that ever happened to him.
不过这是他自己情愿的
Yeah, and that he was trying to decide
如果我的死是将我们都带出痛苦的深渊
If smothering me with a pillow was the best way
的最佳途径
To put us both out of our misery.
在哪里
Okay, where is it?
什么东西
Where is what?
那张写有你刚才说的话的条子在哪里
Where's the note that says that?
把它写下来了吗?    没有
Did you write that down? No.
没
No.
我愿意
Yes.
我要走了  我要去找艾历克斯
I've gotta go. I've gotta find Alex.
去吧
Go, go.
抱歉 我只是...看看乔治在不在这里
Oh, I'm sorry. I was just... I was looking for George.
贝利  已经6点了
Bailey, it's after 6:00.
对  我们安排了一次干涉会
Yes, uh, we scheduled an intervention
以便欧麦利知道我们
So that we could give O'malley a piece of our minds
对他愚蠢参军行为的想法
About this idiotic army business.
他已经走了吗  他根本就没进手术室
Now did he leave already? He never scrubbed in.
他告诉我他已经参军了  我让他回家看看
He told me he was enlisting. I sent him home,
告诉他多花点时间陪陪他的母亲
Told him to spend the day with his mom
在他入伍之前
Since he was leaving so soon.
他今天早上走的
Uh, he took off this morning.
重症监护病房怎么样了
How's his I.C.P.?
非常糟糕
Uh. Worse. O.R. Is expecting us.
-我告诉过让你们结婚的  -我们结婚了
-I thought you were getting married.  -We did.
恭喜
Oh, congratulations.
你们真的打算在手术室里边度过你们的蜜月吗？
You sure you want to start your honeymoon in an o.R.?
我们正打算这么做
We're sure.
你不应该在这里
You can't be in here.
我应该来  并且在这里等你
I'll come and get you in the waiting room.
紧紧握住他的手
Hold his hand until you put him under.
这会让他感觉好一些
It really does make him feel better.
好吧
Okay.
你有一个很棒的朋友
Well, you made a good friend there.
因为你为别人挡车了
I guess that happens when you take a bus for somebody.
好吧
Okay.
我知道这很可怕
I know this is scary,
但是你做了一件很伟大事情
But you do have a great team up there.
你还想写点什么吗
You want to try to write again?
能握住笔吗
Can you hold the pen?
00?
两个0
Double 0...
天哪 天哪
Oh, god! Oh, god.
你叫我 有什么事情吗?
You paged me. What do you need? Well, way to go, dipwad.
跟你妻子说你怎么让她安静下来的吗?
Telling your wife you're trying to figure out how to off her?
别管闲事
Oh, mind your own bus...
等等  你是怎么知道的?
Wait. How did you know that?
她告诉我的
She told me.
你想起来了吗?
You remember?
细枝末节  我全都记起来了
Pillow or morphine. I got the whole thing.
对不起  我刚才不是有意的
Oh, I'm so sorry. I didn't mean that.
当然 我明白
Of course you didn't.
你因为太爱我了所以才会刺激我
You love me too much to shoot me up with morphine
如果换做是我
Even if I asked you to.
面对我当时的愚蠢  天哪 我简直不敢想象
And my stupid corked brain is coming back. Oh, my god. I was so scared.
我想说 无论发生什么 我都会爱你
I mean, I would've loved you no matter what
但是你退缩了
But... you're back
伊兹?
Iz?
伊兹? 杨!
Izzie? Yang!
是乔治   是乔治
It's George! It's George!
是乔治   约翰就是乔治
It's George! John doe is George!
伊兹  睁开眼睛看看我
Izzie, look at me. Open your eyes!
呼谢博德  呼主任和贝利  赶紧!
Page Shepherd. Page the chief and Bailey right now.
我们需要你  欧麦利  你能听到吗  我们需要你
We have you, O'malley. You hear me? We have you.
我们会治好她的  别离开我们  欧麦利  谢博得来了
We'll fix this. Just stay with us. O'malley, it's Shepherd.
你给我乖乖的呆着  懂吗
You're not going anywhere. You understand me?
-血压骤降  -现在把他推出去
B.P.'s dropping. All right, let's put him out, now.
发生什么事情了 是她的肿瘤吗
What happened? Is it her brain?
不 血钾过多 我们无法控制她的心跳
No, it's hyperkalemia. We couldn't control the arrhythmias.
-她血压直线下降  -给她插管
Her pressure's dropping off a cliff. Give me an intubation tray.
艾力克斯
Alex...
她签了不予急救协议  住口  杨
She signed a d.N.R. Shut up, Yang.
她知道这会发生  所以她才签了
She knew this might happen. That's why she signed it.
我可不管她签了什么狗屁协议
I don't give a crap what she signed.
艾力克斯  她不想你这样的
Alex, it's not what she wants.
把急救床推起来
Continuous tone) get a crash cart!
克莱夫  如果她不能...
Karev, if she doesn't...
看着她  推个急救车来
Look at her! Get a crash cart!
把急救车推来  给我些插管
Screw the D.N.R. Hand me those paddles.
-杨  接着按压  -克莱夫  让我来  让我来
Yang, take over compressions. Karev, back up. I got it. I got it.
一  二 三 放下来
One, two, three. And down.
好的慢慢的放下来
Okay, down.
你是否有说过
Did you say it?
我爱你
I love you...
让开
Clear.
我从未想过没有你的生活
I don't ever want to live without you...
你改变了我的生活
You changed my life...
你说过了没有?
Did you say it?
写个计划
Make a plan...
定个目标
Set a goal...
奋斗不息
Work toward it...
但我们总时不时  东张希望
But every now and again, look around...
喝上几杯
Drink it in.
没有为什么
'cause this is it.
我们快失去他了
We're losing him!
到了明天  一切都是过眼云烟
It might all be gone tomorrow.